anastasiabeverlyhills.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy - Anastasia Beverly Hills

At Anastasia Beverly Hills Inc. we are committed to protecting your personal information and respecting your privacy. It is your personal data and we respect that.

This Privacy Policy tells you about how and why we collect and use the personal data which you provide to us or which we collect about you when you interact with us, for example, when you use our website or visit our stores.

We want you to be informed about how we use your data, how we keep it secure and your rights.

We trust this Privacy Policy will answer any questions you have. But if not, please contact us directly at info@anastasiabeverlyhills.com or use the contact details provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.

It is likely that we will need to update this Privacy Policy from time-to-time by updating this page. We will notify you of any significant changes, but we encourage you to come back and review it from time-to-time.

**Ensuring the Lawful Use of Your Data**

We will only use your personal data where we have a lawful basis to use it. We will only use your data where: (a) it is necessary for us to perform our contract with you (for example, to fulfill your order); or (b) it might reasonably be expected as part of running our business; and (c) it does not adversely impact your interests, rights or freedoms.

For example, we might use your purchase history to send you personalized offers. We might also combine your shopping history to identify trends and improve our ability to keep up with demand and develop the right new products for our customers. Please contact us using the contact details provided at the end of this Privacy Policy if you would like further information about this.

We may sometimes need to use data to comply with our legal obligations. One example is to provide details related to fraud to law enforcement agencies. In other instances, we will ask for your consent to use your data, for example, where you sign-up to receive our email newsletters.

Further details regarding our use of your personal information are provided below.

**What Information We Collect from You and How We Use It**

Information we collect about you and how we will use it depends on how you interact with us. For example, you might place an order on our Website, contact us with a question by email or phone, make a purchase, or book an appointment in one of the stores that carry our products. The information discussed below provides some examples of the information we collect about you and how we will use it.

We will collect personal data needed to identify you, such as your name, username, password and date of birth. We will also collect your contact details, such as your email address, telephone number and billing/delivery address. We will use your information as detailed below.

**To fulfill our contract with you:**

  * To fulfill your order, for example, by delivering your products to you or to contact you about your order where necessary

**Legitimate business purposes:**

  * To allow you to create an account with us

  * To allow you to book an appointment with us or to attend an event

  * To communicate with you your order or booking, if you have asked a question or sent us a complaint

  * To allow you to complete any surveys we send you (if you wish to), or to comment on or review our products or services, to help us improve them

  * To support fraud prevention and detection

**Where you consent:**

  * To send you email newsletters to keep you up-to-date about our products, services, and latest offers, which we think will interest you (only where you consent)

  * To allow you to enter competitions, events, or prize draws run by us

We will use the information you provide when you contact us by telephone, by email, by post or on social media as detailed below.

**Legitimate business purposes:**

  * To provide you with the support and customer service you have requested

We may track technical information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns. We collect this personal data by using cookies, server logs and other similar technologies. We provide details regarding how we process and use cookies, which can be found in our Cookies Policy. We will use this information as detailed below.

**Legitimate business purposes:**

  * To administer and to improve our Website, to ensure it is presented in the

  * most effective manner for you and to give you the best Website experience and to allow you to participate in interactive features of our Website if you choose to do so

  * For data analysis, testing, research and statistical statistics to help us to improve our products and services

  * To keep our Website safe and secure

  * To make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our Website about products or services that may interest you or them

  * To measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we direct to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you

We may gather additional information you choose to provide, including your hair color, eye color and skin tone. We will use this information as detailed below.

**Legitimate business purposes:**

  * To assist us to provide you with a more personalized beauty experience

You do not have to give us any of the personal data discussed above. But, if you do not provide us with certain information, we may not be able to ship you with the goods and provide the services you have requested from us.

The forms you fill in on our Website and in stores that carry our products will make it clear what information we need to provide the product or service you are requesting and what information you can decide whether to provide. To help us form a better, overall understanding of you as a customer, we combine your personal data, for example, your shopping history.

**1\. AUTOMATED DECISION MAKING**

We do not currently carry out automated decision-making using information we hold about you.

**2\. SHARING YOUR DATA**

**SHARING YOUR DATA WITH THIRD PARTIES WE TRUST**

We share your personal data with third parties we trust to allow us to provide our services to you. When we do share your data with these third parties, we only provide the information they need to perform the service. We have written contracts in place with them requiring they only use your data for the purpose we specify to them and that your privacy is secure and respected.

The third parties we trust include the following:

  * Companies that help us fulfill your orders: FedEx, USPS

  * Professional service providers such as website hosting providers, system providers, website analytics providers, advertisers and appointment booking providers, who help us run our business: SalesForce Commerce Cloud and Marketing Cloud, Google Analytics, BrightEdge, JazzHR, Narvar;

  * Direct marketing companies who help us manage our electronic communications with you: ExactTarget, Social Annex, Windsor Circle;

  * Social Media or Web platforms to show you products that might interest you while you are browsing the internet: Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, YouTube, Gmail;

  * Companies that send segmented, personalized marketing communications on our behalf: Windsor Circle; and

  * Credit reference agencies, law enforcement and fraud prevention agencies, so that we can help tackle fraud: CyberSource, PayPal

We may also share your personal data connected in a business transaction. Those transactions include a merger, acquisition by another company, an investment in our company or a sale of all or a portion of our assets). In these circumstances, we may need to share your personal data with a prospective buyer, investor and external professional advisors, such as accountants, insurers, lawyers or financial institutions.

We may be required by law to share your personal data with the police, administrative authorities or other enforcement, regulatory or Government bodies.

We will only share your personal data with third parties for them to use for their own direct marketing purposes when you have given your consent for us to do so.

We will only share your personal data with third parties for them to use for their own direct marketing purposes when you have given your consent for us to do so.

For more information on the privacy policies of our partners who act as independent data controllers, please direct your inquiries to:

DHL International N.V. / S.A.

Woluwelaan 151

1831 Diegem

Belgium

BE 0406 796 224

<http://www.dhl.com/en/legal.html#privacy>

Ingenico eCommerce Solutions SPRL (only acting as a Contracted Controller for the Fraud Expert tool)

Boulevard de la Woluwe, 102

1200 Brussels

Belgium

BE 0459.360.623

<https://payment-services.ingenico.com/be/en/cookie-policy>

European Merchant Services B.V.

Diemen

The Netherlands

NL 34226533

<https://emspay.eu/privacy-information-notice>

Paypal Europe SARL & Cie, SCA

5th Floor, 22-24 Boulevard Royal

2449 Luxemburg

R.C.S Luxemburg B 118 349

<https://www.paypal.com/be/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full?locale.x=en_BE>

**3\. INFORMATION WE RECEIVE FROM THIRD PARTIES**

We may receive information about you from third parties, such as: (a) companies with which we run competitions and events, such as trade shows; or from organizations we work with, or from publicly available sources, such as Companies House, or information which is published in the media,

Depending on your settings or the privacy policies of social media or messaging services, such as Facebook, Instagram, Twitter or WhatsApp, we may collect information about you from these sources, with your permission.

We may combine the information you have given us, with information obtained from other sources, but we will only do this when we have a lawful basis to do so.

**4\. SEEING ADVERTISEMENTS FOR OUR WEBSITE ONLINE**

We, like many other companies, target Anastasia Beverly Hills ads and banners when you are browsing on apps and other websites. We do this by way of various ad exchanges and digital marketing networks.

We use various advertising technologies, for instance, ad tag, cookies, pixels, identifiers and web beacons. We also use services offered by some sites and social networks, for example, Facebook's Custom Audiences. The ads and banners you see are based on information that we hold about you, or on your prior use of our Website. Examples include: (a) products you have browsed previously; (b) content you have read on our Website; or (c) content you have read on Anastasia Beverly Hills’ banners or ads that you previously reviewed.

**5\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

We are a global business and some of our group companies and service providers are located in other countries.

As a result, it may be necessary for the personal data that we collect from you to be transferred to or accessed from outside the US so we can provide our services more effectively.

If we do this, we have procedures in place to ensure your data receives the necessary protections. Any transfer of your personal data will follow applicable laws and we will treat the information according to the principles in this Privacy Policy.

If you would like further information, please contact us using the contact details provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.

**6\. NON-US CUSTOMERS**

If you are based outside the US and place an order on the Website, your personal data will be accessed in the US by Anastasia Beverly Hills Inc. and the third parties detailed above.

**7\. HOW LONG WILL WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL DATA?**

We will only keep your personal data as long as we need to for the reason(s) we collected it, as discussed in this Privacy Policy.

We may also retain some of your personal data if we are required to do so for legal purposes. Examples include: (a) meeting our legal or regulatory requirements; or (b) preventing fraud and abuse.

**8\. UPDATING AND CORRECTING**

It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. If you have an account with us, please keep your details up-to-date.

**9\. SECURITY**

We are committed to securing your personal data. We have put in place suitable physical, electronic, contractual and managerial procedures, including our Information Security Management System and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption, to protect your personal data.

**10\. THIRD-PARTY LINKS**

Our Website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, we do not have any control over third-party websites and they will be governed by their own privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy.

**11\. HOW CAN I UNSUBSCRIBE FROM MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS?**

We enjoy keeping you up-to-date by email about our latest products, services, offers and events. But if you decide that you do not want to receive these communications at any point, you can unsubscribe as follows:

  * (1) Email us at: info@anastasiabeverlyhills.com or click on the unsubscribe button on the bottom of any email we send you; or

  * (2) If you have an account with us, you can also unsubscribe by going to the Account Information page on the Anastasia Beverly Hills website, clicking on Newsletters, and unsubscribing to general subscription.

**12\. YOUR RIGHTS**

You have the following rights regarding the personal information we hold about you to request:

  * Access to the personal data we hold about you (commonly known as a "data subject access request") including a copy of it;

  * The correction of the personal information that we hold about you if it is not complete or accurate. But if you hold an account with us, you may be able to do this in certain cases yourself by visiting the Account Information page on the Anastasia Beverly Hills website;

  * The deletion or removal of personal data we hold about you where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it or where you have exercised your right to object to processing (see below);

  * For our processing of your personal information to be restricted to certain circumstances, for example if you want to establish its accuracy or the reason for processing it; and

  * To obtain a copy of the personal information you have provided us with and to reuse it elsewhere or to ask us to transfer it to a third party of your choice.

We may ask you for proof of your identity before dealing with your request, as a security measure to protect your data.

**Right to Object**

Where we are processing your personal data on the basis of our legitimate interests, you can ask us to stop processing it. We must do so unless we believe we have an overriding legitimate reason to continue processing your personal data.

**13\. CONTACTING US**

If you have any queries, comments or requests regarding this Privacy Policy, you have a complaint, or you would like to exercise any of your rights set out above, you can contact us in the following ways:

  * By email at info@anastasiabeverlyhills.com; or

  * By post at Consumer Relations, Anastasia Beverly Hills Inc., 10635 Santa Monica Blvd, Ste 300 Los Angeles CA 90025

**14\. TERMS AND CONDITIONS – SMS DELIVERY ALERTS**

Anastasia Beverly Hills offers its customers the convenient option to receive mobile alerts about their orders via SMS messages. Standard message and data rates most likely apply. SMS updates are unavailable for international phone numbers and for orders shipped via USPS (including domestic PO boxes and Puerto Rico).

At any time, you can reply STOP to opt out. 

You must be 18 years old or older to participate or have parent/guardian permission. U.S. residents only. 

**How to enroll**

During the checkout process, you will be prompted to provide your mobile number and to agree to these Terms & Conditions. 

By enrolling in Mobile Order Alerts, you acknowledge and agree that Order Alert Messages about your order(s) will be sent to your mobile number. You also acknowledge and agree that those with access to that mobile number or the carrier account may be able to view your order information.

Participation in Mobile Order Alerts is not a condition of purchase. However, if you decide to participate in Mobile Order Alerts, then there is a requirement that you agree to these Terms and Conditions. 

**How to opt-out**

You can easily stop receiving Mobile Order Alert messages from Anastasia Beverly Hills for your current order. You simply opt-out of Mobile Order Alerts by texting the word ‘STOP’ in a reply text message to one of the status Order Alert Messages you receive from us.

Once you have taken this step to opt-out of Mobile Order Alerts, you will receive a final confirmation Mobile Order Alert message. After that, no further Mobile Order Alert messages will be sent to your mobile number concerning any orders, unless you opt-in for future orders.

**Message and data rates**

Message and data rates most likely apply, depending your carrier. All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider.

Copyright © 2018 Anastasia Beverly Hills, Inc. All worldwide rights reserved.
